Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
- Princeton Football Film Reels, 1935-1990; 2187 items
  - 1984-1985, 252 items
    - 1985 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1985 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1985 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1985 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Defense 1))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Defense 1))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Defense 2))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Defense 2))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 1))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 2))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 3))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Full Game 4))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Kicking))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Kicking))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Offense 1))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Offense 1))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Offense 2))
    - 1985 William and Mary (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 William and Mary (Offense 2))
    - 1985 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1985 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1985 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1985 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1985 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1985 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1985 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1985 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1985 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1985 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1985 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1985 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1985 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1985 Yale (Offense 2))
  - 1986-1987, 279 items
    - 1986 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1986 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1986 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1986 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1986 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1986 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1986 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1986 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1986 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Kicking))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Kicking))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Lehigh (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Lehigh (Offense 2))
    - 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1986 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Kicking))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Kicking))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Northwestern (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Northwestern (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1986 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1986 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Defense 1))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Defense 1))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Defense 2))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Defense 2))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Kicking))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Kicking))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Offense 1))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Offense 1))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Offense 2))
    - 1986 William and Mary (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 William and Mary (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1986 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1986 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1986 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1986 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1986 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1986 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1986 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1986 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1986 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1986 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1986 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1987 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1987 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1987 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1987 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1987 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1987 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1987 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1987 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Davidson (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Davidson (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Davidson (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Davidson (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Davidson (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Davidson (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Davidson (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Davidson (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Davidson (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Kicking))
    - 1987 Davidson (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Kicking))
    - 1987 Davidson (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Davidson (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Davidson (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Davidson (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Davidson (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1987 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1987 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Kicking))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Kicking))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Lehigh (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Lehigh (Offense 2))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1987 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1987 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Penn (Full Game4), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Full Game4))
    - 1987 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1987 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1987 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1987 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1987 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1987 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1987 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1987 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1987 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1987 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1987 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1987 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1987 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1987 Yale (Offense 2))
  - 1988-1990, 262 items
    - 1988 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1988 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1988 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1988 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1988 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1988 Bucknell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Bucknell (Defense 1))
    - 1988 Bucknell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Bucknell (Defense 2))
    - 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 1))
    - 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 2))
    - 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 3))
    - 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1988 Bucknell (Full Game 4))